<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">5</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">29</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">29</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>

<entry key='tokens-field-of-vision'>true</entry>
<entry key='subjects-field-of-vision'>true</entry>
<!-- enable sanctioning -->
<entry key="sanction-type">real-time</entry>
<entry key="sanction-cost">1</entry>
<entry key="sanction-multiplier">2</entry>

<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<!-- before this round begins, we have a chat session -->
<entry key="chat-enabled">true</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 6 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
Round 6 is the same as round 5.</p>
<p>
The length of this round is again four minutes.
</p>
<p>
If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="last-round-debriefing">
<![CDATA[
<p>
This was the last round, but not the end of the experiment. We will now
determine your payments. While we are doing this, we request that you
carefully fill out a brief survey.
</p>
<p>
When we are ready we will call you one by one to the room next door. We will
pay you there in private. Please wait until your computer number is called,
and then proceed to the room next door to turn in your computer number and
your survey. 
</p>
<p>
Please answer the survey carefully and thank you for participating. 
</p>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="chat-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<p>
You can chat with the other participants in your group during this round.
You may communicate about any aspect of the experiment that you would like to
discuss with other participants with whom you have been matched. You may not promise
them side-payments after the experiment is completed or threaten them with any
consequence after the experiment is finished. We are monitoring the chat traffic
while you chat. If we see that somebody reveals his or her identity, we have to stop
the experiment and remove the whole group from which this person is a member out of
this room.
</p>
<p>
You will see other participants labeled as "1", "2","3", "4", or "5" in the chat
box.  You can send a chat message by typing into the textfield and pressing the
enter key.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='trust-game-instructions'>
<![CDATA[
<h3>Task</h3>
<p>
You will be matched with another person in your group, but you will not know who
that person is.  And that person will not know who you are.  You make decisions for
the case you are drawn to be player 1 and the case you will be player 2.  The
results of the decisions are given to you at the end of the whole experiment.
</p>

<p>
The person drawn to be player 1 has the following decision to make. You will receive
an endowment of one dollar and decide how much to keep and how much to send to
another person in your group. 
</p>

<p>
The amount you send to the other person will be tripled and then given to the person
in your group with whom you have been matched.  That person will decide how much to
keep and how much to send back to you.  For example, if you send 0 extra credit
points to the other person, 0 extra credit points will be sent to the other person.
However, if you write 3 extra credit points on the form, 9 extra credit points will
be sent to the person.  The other person would then decide how much to return to
you.
</p>

<p>
Player 2 has the following decision to make. You have to chose for each of the 4
possible cases how much to receive from player 1 how much to keep and how much to
send back to player 1.
We ask you to fill in the tables for player 1 as well as for player 2, and we will
drawn whether you are player 1 or 2 after you have made the decisions.
</p>

<p>
Are there any questions?  If you have a question, raise your hand and I will try to
answer it.                                              
</p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
