<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">26</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">26</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
<entry key='voting-enabled'>true</entry>
<entry key="instructions">
    <![CDATA[
    <h1>Important New Instructions</h1>
    <h2>Reducing Other Player's Earnings</h2>
    <hr>
<p>
Round {self.roundNumber} is about to begin.  You will now have the option to reduce the
earnings of another participant at a cost to your own earnings by typing that
participants' number key from 1 to {self.clientsPerGroup}.
</p>
    <ul>
        <li>Each player in your group has a number from 1 to {self.clientsPerGroup}.  If
            you press a number key 1-{self.clientsPerGroup}, you will reduce the number
            of tokens that player has collected during the round by
            {self.sanctionPenalty} tokens. This will also reduce your own token amount by
            {self.sanctionCost} token. The decision whether or when to use this option is
            up to you. 
        </li>
        <li>When you reduce the number of tokens of another participant, they will
            receive a message stating that you have reduced their tokens. Likewise, if
            another participant reduces your number of tokens, you will also receive a
            message. These messages will be displayed on the bottom of your screen.
        </li>
        <li>If your tokens are being reduced or you are reducing another participant's
            tokens, you will receive some visual cues.  When your tokens are being reduced
            your yellow dot will turn red briefly with a blue background.  The participant
            currently reducing your tokens will turn purple with a white background.
        </li>
        <li>You may reduce the earnings of other participants as long as (1) there are
            tokens remaining on the screen and (2) both you and the other participant
            have a positive number of tokens collected during the round.  <b>Each time</b>
            you press the numeric key corresponding to another participant your token
            amount is reduced by <b>{self.sanctionCost}</b>, and their token amount is reduced by
            <b>{self.sanctionPenalty}</b>.  
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p>
        The length of this round is {duration}.
    </p>
<h2>Strategy Reminder</h2>
<hr>
    <p>
        The strategy your group voted for is: 
    </p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>{first(self.selectedRules)}</b></li>
        </ul>
<p><b>Do you have any questions?</b> If you have any questions at this time, raise your hand and someone will come over to your station and answer it.</p>
    ]]>
</entry>

<entry key='voting-results'>
    <![CDATA[
    <h1>Voting Results</h1>
    <h2>Selected Strategy</h2>
    <hr>
    <p><b> {first(selectedRules)} </b></p>
    {if (tiebreaker)}
    <p><b>NOTE:</b> There was a tie and selected strategy listed here was randomly selected as the winner.</p>
    <h2>Other Nominated Strategies</h2>
    <hr>
        <ol>
            {rest(selectedRules): {selectedRule | <li> <b>{selectedRule}</b></li>}}
        </ol>
    {endif}
    ]]>
</entry>

<entry key='initial-voting-instructions'>
    <![CDATA[
<h1>Important New Instructions</h1>
<h2>Strategies for managing how players collect tokens for the rest of the experiment</h2>
<hr>
<p>
In a moment, you will have the option to implement one of six strategies for how you
and the three other people in your group collect tokens for the rest of the
experiment.
</p>
<h2>Procedure for Deciding the Strategy</h2>
<hr>
<p>
    Each of the {clientsPerGroup} people in your group can nominate one of the six
    potential strategies.  The single strategy that receives the most nominations
    wins.
</p>
<p>
    <b>If there is a tie</b>, one of the tied options will be selected at random by
    the computer.  Each of the tied strategies will have an equal chance of being
    selected.
</p>
<h2>Implementation</h2>
<hr>
    <p>Neither the computer nor the experimenter will intervene to implement the
        strategy.
    </p>

    <p>
        <b>Do you have any questions?</b>  If you have any questions at this time,
        raise your hand and someone will come over to your station and answer it.
    </p>
    ]]>
</entry>


<entry key='voting-instructions'>
<![CDATA[
<h1>Strategy Nomination Instructions</h1>
<hr>
<p>
To nominate a strategy, click the button to the right of the one you choose, and
then click "submit." The computer will tally the nominations and then report the
results on the next screen. The results will be presented to each person in
your group.
</p>
<h2>Your selection will be anonymous</h2>
<hr>
<p>
The identity of people who nominated a particular strategy will NOT be revealed.
Therefore, neither you nor the experimenter will know who nominated a particular
strategy.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='external-survey-enabled'>true</entry>
<entry key='survey-url'>
    <![CDATA[https://qtrial.qualtrics.com/SE/?SID=SV_cLX7jnYikmD9eSM&SURVEY_ID={surveyId}]]>
</entry>

<entry key='sanction-type'>real-time</entry>
<entry key="sanction-cost">1</entry>
<entry key="sanction-multiplier">2</entry>
</properties>
