<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="practice-round">false</entry>
<entry key='resource-width'>8</entry>
<entry key='resource-depth'>8</entry>
<entry key='resource-scale'>32</entry>
<entry key="duration">900</entry>
<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
<entry key="private-property">false</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="quiz-enabled">false</entry>
<entry key="chat-radius">64</entry>
<entry key="seconds-per-year">30</entry>
<entry key="regrowth-rate">.01</entry>
<entry key="tokens-per-fruits">10</entry>
<entry key="experiment-type">forestry</entry>
<entry key="maximum-resource-age">10</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 2 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
The actual round will now begin. The duration of this round is 15 minutes.
For review, here is a list of important actions and respective keys:
</p>
<p>
<b>Moving your avatar:</b> You can move your avatar by pressing the <b>W</b>,
<b>A</b>, <b>S</b>, <b>D</b> keys or via the arrow keys. <b>W</b> or the
<b>Up</b> arrow key will move your avatar forward while <b>S</b> or the
<b>Down</b> arrow key will move it backward. <b>A</b> or the <b>Left</b> arrow
key will rotate the avatar to its left while <b>D</b> or the <b>Right</b>
arrow key will rotate it to its right.
</p>
<p>
<b>Cutting a tree:</b> Cutting a tree is a two step process.
First you need to select the tree you wish to cut. You can do this by standing
next to the tree and pressing the <b>Q</b> key. You will see the selected tree
changing its color to blue. Then you can cut the selected tree by pressing the
<b>E</b> key. You will see that the avatar moves its axe to cut the tree. The
bigger the tree the move effort the avatar needs to make to cut the tree. When
the tree is cut, you will see tokens added to your total at the top of the
screen. 
</p>
<p>
<b>Collecting fruits:</b> Collecting fruits is also a two step process. 
First you need to select the tree you wish collect fruits from. You can do
this by standing next to the tree and pressing the key <b>Q</b>. You will see
the selected tree changing its color to blue. Then you can collect the fruits
by pressing the key <b>X</b>. You will see that the fruits are falling down,
representing the fruit harvest. On the top of the screen you will see that
tokens are added to your total.
</p>
<p>
<b>Chatting with other players:</b> A chat box is present at the bottom of the
screen. When another player is in the neighborhood, you can click on that
avatar using the left mouse button to start a chat. You will see the character
associated with the selected avatar (<i>A</i>, <i>B</i>, <i>C</i> or <i>D</i>)
appearing in the chat box indicating that you can send messages to that
player.
</p>

]]>
</entry>


</properties>
