<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Communication and Motives of Self-Governance Phase 1 Configuration</comment>
<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>
<entry key='clients-per-group'>4</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">26</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">26</entry>
<entry key='regrowth-rate'>0.01</entry>
<entry key='repeat'>3</entry>
<entry key="quiz">true</entry>
<entry key="q1">T</entry>
<entry key="q2">T</entry>
<entry key="q3">B</entry>
<entry key="q4">B</entry>
<entry key="q5">F</entry>
<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Round {self.roundIndexLabel} Instructions</h1>
<hr>
<p>
    The length of this round is {self.duration} seconds. As in the practice round you can collect green tokens. However,
    this time you will earn <b>{dollarsPerToken}</b> for each token collected. You <b>cannot</b> reset the
    distribution of green tokens. 
</p>
<h3>Groups</h3>
<hr>
<p>
In this round the renewable resource will become four times bigger.  You will share
this larger environment with three other random players in this room.  Each
participant in the room has been randomly assigned to one of several equal-sized
{self.clientsPerGroup} person groups and everyone in your group has been randomly
assigned a number from 1 to {self.clientsPerGroup}.  You will stay in the same group for
the entire experiment, and each person's number from 1 to {self.clientsPerGroup} will
remain the same throughout the experiment. The other members of your group will
appear on the screen as blue dots <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-other.gif">
with a white number embedded in the dot.
</p>
<p>
    In each round of the token task, you can see how many tokens each player has
    collected at the top right corner of the screen.  On the top left corner of the
    screen you will see the remaining time in the round.
</p>
<h3>Anonymity</h3>
<hr>
<p>
    Because group membership was randomly assigned by the computer, neither you nor
    the experimenter will be able to identify which person in the room has been
    assigned to a particular group or number within a group.  Your anonymity is
    guaranteed.
</p>
<h3>Tokens</h3>
<hr>
    <p>
        Each group has its own set of token resources.
    </p>
<p><b>Do you have any questions so far?</b>  If you have any questions at this time, raise your hand and someone will come over to your station and answer it.</p>
]]>

</entry>
<entry key="quiz-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h2>Quiz</h2>
<hr>
<p>
    Before we begin the actual round please answer the following questions to make sure you understand the instructions.
    You will receive {quizCorrectAnswerReward} lab dollars for each correct answer. When you are finished, please click
    submit.
</p>
<br>
<form>
<span class='q1'>Q1. Once you have collected all the tokens on the screen, no new tokens will appear.</span> <br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="T">Correct<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="F">Incorrect<br>
<br><br>
<span class='q2'>Q2. Tokens regenerate faster (new tokens appear faster) when empty spots are surrounded by more tokens.</span> <br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="T">Correct<br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="F">Incorrect<br>
<br><br>
<span class='q3'>Q3. Which of the following sequences is not possible, A, B, or C?</span> <br>
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/possible-sequences-abc.png" /><br>
<input type="radio" name="q3" value="A">A<br>
<input type="radio" name="q3" value="B">B<br>
<input type="radio" name="q3" value="C">C<br>
<br><br>
<span class='q4'>Q4. Each token you collect is worth? (select the correct value)</span> <br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="A">$.01<br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="B">$.02<br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="C">$.03<br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="D">$.04<br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="E">$.05<br>
<br><br>
<span class='q5'>Q5. The amount of money you can earn today only depends on the decisions you make?</span> <br>
<input type="radio" name="q5" value="T">Correct<br>
<input type="radio" name="q5" value="F">Incorrect<br>
<input type="submit" name="submit" value="Submit"><br>
</form>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key='quiz-results'>
<![CDATA[
    <h2>Quiz Results</h2>
    <hr>
        <p>
            {if (allCorrect)}
            You have answered all the questions correctly and earned <b>{totalQuizEarnings}</b> in lab dollars.
            {else}
            You answered {numberCorrect} out of {totalQuestions} questions correctly and earned <b>{totalQuizEarnings}</b> in lab dollars.  Questions you've answered
            incorrectly are highlighted in red.  Please see below for more details.
            {endif}
        </p>
        <br><hr>
<form>
<span class='q1'>Q1. Once you have collected all the tokens on the screen, no new tokens will appear.</span> <br>
    <b>
        This is correct. New tokens only appear if there is at least one token on the screen.
    </b>
<br><br>
<span class='q2'>Q2. Tokens regenerate faster (new tokens appear faster) when empty spots are surrounded by more tokens.</span> <br>
    <b>
        This is correct. Tokens regenerate faster when empty spots are surrounded by more tokens.
    </b>
    <br><br>
<span class='q3'>Q3. Which of the following sequences is not possible, A, B, or C?</span> <br>
    <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/possible-sequences-abc.png" /><br>
    <b>
        Sequence B is not possible, new tokens will not appear once they are all gone.
    </b>
    <br><br>
<span class='q4'>Q4. Each token you collect is worth? (select the correct value).</span> <br>
    <b>
        Each token you collect will be worth $0.02. For example, if you collect 10 tokens you will earn $0.20 (twenty
        cents). If you collect 50 tokens you will earn $1.00 (one dollar), and if you collect 100 tokens or more, you
        would earn $2.00 or more.
    </b>
    <br><br>
<span class='q5'>Q5. The amount of money you can earn today only depends on the decisions you make?</span>
<br>
    <b>
        This is incorrect. The amount of money you earn today will depend on the decisions you make and the decisions
        that the other people in your group make. Each person’s decisions to collect tokens affects the number of tokens
        (money) available for the other people in group.
    </b>
    <br><br>
</form>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
