<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="practice-round">true</entry>
<entry key='resource-width'>8</entry>
<entry key='resource-depth'>8</entry>
<entry key='resource-scale'>32</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>
<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
<entry key="private-property">false</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="quiz-enabled">false</entry>
<entry key="chat-radius">64</entry>
<entry key="seconds-per-year">30</entry>
<entry key="regrowth-rate">.01</entry>
<entry key="tokens-per-fruits">10</entry>
<entry key="experiment-type">abstract</entry>
<entry key="maximum-resource-age">10</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 3 Instructions</h3>
<p>
Round 3 is another practice round.  This time you will be placed in a 3-D
world where you can collect tokens by harvesting pillars and rings at the top
of the pillars.
</p>
<p>
The world consists of pillars which grow slowly over time. When a pillar
becomes large enough a yellow component will appear at its top. You can collect
this part from a pillar or you can collect the pillar itself. The older the pillar
the more tokens you collect by harvesting it. A pillar which is one minute old
leads to 5 tokens, while a pillar that is four minutes old gives you 25 tokens.
After 4 minutes the pillar will not grow any further. If a pillar is harvested, it 
will take some time before a new pillar appears. A pillar will be crowned with a yellow 
component when it reaches an age of 5 minutes. You can collect this yellow component, 
which generates 10 tokens per harvest. When you have collected the yellow part, a new part 
will be added as illustrated in the figure below. The pillars can generate yellow parts indefinitely.
</p>
<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td align="center">
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/abstract.jpg"></td>
</tr>
</table> 
You will share the environment with three other participants. You will appear on
the screen as an avatar represented as a ball.
</p>
<p>
<b>Moving your avatar:</b> You can move your avatar by pressing the <b>W</b>,
<b>A</b>, <b>S</b>, <b>D</b> keys or via the arrow keys. <b>W</b> or the
<b>Up</b> arrow key will move your avatar forward while <b>S</b> or the
<b>Down</b> arrow key will move it backward. <b>A</b> or the <b>Left</b> arrow
key will rotate the avatar to its left while <b>D</b> or the <b>Right</b>
arrow key will rotate it to its right.
</p>
<p>
<b>Harvesting a purple pillar:</b> Harvesting a pillar is a two step process. 
First you need to select the pillar you wish to harvest. You can do this by standing 
next to the pillar and pressing the key <b>Q</b> key. You will see the selected pillar 
changing its color to green. Then you can harvest the selected pillar by pressing the
<b>E</b> key. You will see that the avatar bumps against the selected pillar. The
bigger the pillar the more effort the avatar needs to make to harvest the pillar. When
the pillar is harvested, you will see tokens added to your total at the top of the
screen.
</p>
<p>
<b>Collecting yellow components:</b> Collecting yellow component of a pillar is also a two step process. 
First you need to select the pillar you wish collect component from. You can do
this by standing next to the pillar and pressing the key <b>Q</b>. You will see
the selected pillar changing its color to green. Then you can collect the yellow component at the top of the pillar 
by pressing the key <b>X</b>. On the top of the screen you will see that
tokens are added to your total.
</p>
<p>
<b>Chatting with other players:</b> A chat box is present at the bottom of the
screen. When another player is in the neighborhood, you can click on that
avatar using the left mouse button to start a chat. You will see the character
associated with the selected avatar (<i>A</i>, <i>B</i>, <i>C</i> or <i>D</i>)
appearing in the chat box indicating that you can send messages to that
player.
</p>
<hr>
<h3>Practice Round Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
You will now have four minutes to practice with the experimental environment.
You will share the environment with three other participants. Make sure you
try out the chat option, the harvesting of a pillars and the collection of yellow components.
<p><center><b>Please do not communicate with any other participant.</b></center></p>
<p>If you have any questions please raise your hand. <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b></p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
