<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">26</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">26</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 1 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
This is the first round of the experiment. The length of the round is 4
minutes. As in the practice round you can collect green tokens but now
you will earn <b>two cents</b> for each token collected.  You <b>cannot</b>
reset the distribution of green tokens. 
</p>
<p>
In this round the renewable resource will become five times bigger.  You will share this
larger environment with four other players in this room that have been randomly
selected.  Each group's resource environment is distinct from the other groups.
</p>
<p>
Each of you has been assigned a number from 1 to 5.  These numbers will remain the
same throughout the experiment but you will <b>not</b> be able to identify which
person in the room has been assigned which number, so your anonymity is guaranteed.  
</p>

<p>
The other four players will appear on the screen as blue dots 
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-other.gif"> with a white
number embedded in the dot.  On the top right corner of the screen you can see 
how many tokens each player has collected. On the top left corner of the screen you can see 
a clock that displays the remaining time in the round.</p>
<p>Since you can only see the resource within your vision you may neither see all 
the other participants nor all the resource units. The figure below indicates the 
vision range compared to the whole environment</p>
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/vision-range.jpg">
<p>
If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
