<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">5</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">29</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">29</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>

<!-- enable field of vision for tokens and subjects -->
<entry key='tokens-field-of-vision'>true</entry>
<entry key='subjects-field-of-vision'>true</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<!-- before this round begins, we have a chat session -->
<entry key="chat-enabled">true</entry>

<!-- enable sanctioning -->
<entry key="sanction-type">real-time</entry>
<entry key="sanction-cost">1</entry>
<entry key="sanction-multiplier">2</entry>

<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>

<!-- enable quiz -->
<entry key='quiz'>true</entry>
<entry key='q1'>B</entry>
<entry key='q2'>C</entry>
<entry key='q3'>B</entry>
<entry key='q4'>B</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 1 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
This is the first round of the experiment. The length of the round is 4
minutes. As in the practice round you can collect green tokens but now
you will earn <b>two cents</b> for each token collected.  You <b>cannot</b>
reset the distribution of green tokens. 
</p>
<p>
In this round the renewable resource will become five times bigger.  You will
share this larger environment with four other players in this room that have
been randomly selected.  Each group's resource environment is distinct from the
other groups. 
</p>
<p>
Each of you has been assigned a number from 1 to 5.  These numbers will remain
the same throughout the experiment but you will not be able to identify which
person in the room has been assigned which number, so your anonymity is
guaranteed.  
</p>
<p>
The other four players will appear on the screen as blue dots <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-other.gif"> with a white number embedded in the
dot.  On the top right corner of the screen you can see how many tokens each
player has collected. On the top left corner of the screen you can see a clock
that displays the remaining time in the round. Since you can only see the
resource within your vision you may neither see all the other participants nor
all the resource units. The figure below indicates the vision range compared
to the whole environment
</p>
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/vision-range.jpg">
<p><b>Do you have any questions so far?</b></p>
<p>
Before the next round starts you can anonymously communicate by text messages
for four minutes with the other participants in your group. You can use this
opportunity to discuss the experiment and coordinate your actions to improve
your earnings. You may not promise side-payments after the experiment is
completed or make any threats. You are also not allowed to reveal your real
identity. We are monitoring the chat traffic while you chat.
</p>
<p>
During the next round you will have the option to reduce the earnings of another
participant at a cost to your own earnings.
</p>
<ul>
<li>If you press the numeric key 1-5 corresponding to another participant, you
will reduce the number of tokens they have collected in this round by two
tokens. This will also reduce your own token amount by one token. The decision
whether or when to use this option is up to you. 
<li>When you reduce the number of tokens of another participant, they will
receive a message stating that you have reduced their tokens. Likewise, if
another participant reduces your number of tokens, you will also receive a
message. These messages will be displayed on the bottom of your screen.
<li>If your tokens are being reduced or you are reducing another participant's
tokens, you will receive some visual cues.  When you are sanctioned your yellow dot will turn red briefly with a blue background.  The participant sanctioning you will turn purple with a white background.
<li>You may sanction other participants as long as there are
tokens remaining on the screen and while both you and the other participant
have a positive number of tokens collected during the round.  <b>Each time</b>
you press the numeric key corresponding to another participant your token
amount is reduced by <b>one</b>, and their token amount is reduced by
<b>two</b>.  <b>Note:</b> You can only remove tokens from a participant that is
visible to you.
</ul>
<p>

<p>
The length of this round is four minutes.
</p>
<p>
If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="chat-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<p>
You can now chat with the other participants in your group for 4 minutes
total. During the chat round, you may communicate about any aspect of the
experiment that you would like to discuss with other participants with whom
you have been matched. You may not promise them side-payments after the
experiment is completed or threaten them with any consequence after the
experiment is finished. We are monitoring the chat traffic while you chat. If
we see that somebody reveals his or her identity, we have to stop the
experiment and remove the whole group from which this person is a member out
of this room.
</p>
<p>
You will see other participants labeled as "1", "2","3", "4", or "5" in the
chat box.  You can send a chat message by typing into the textfield at the
bottom of the screen and pressing the "enter" key on your keyboard.  
</p>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="quiz-instructions">                       
<![CDATA[                                             
<p>Before the next round begins you must complete the quiz below.  You can
only continue when you have answered all questions correctly.  If an error is
made you will need to answer the questions again.
</p>

<form>
<span class='q1'>Q1. Each time I press the numeric keys between 1-5 my tokens will be reduced
by:</span><br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="A">A. 0 tokens<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="B">B. 1 token<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="C">C. 2 tokens<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="D">D. 4 tokens<br>
<br><br>

<span class='q2'>Q2. Each time I press the numeric keys between 1-5 the number of tokens of the
corresponding participant is reduced by:</span><br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="A">A. 0 tokens<br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="B">B. 1 token<br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="C">C. 2 tokens<br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="D">D. 4 tokens<br>
<br><br>

<span class='q3'>Q3. The background of your yellow dot <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-self.gif"> turns blue.  What does this represent?</span><br>
<input type="radio" name="q3" value="A">A. You collected a token<br>
<input type="radio" name="q3" value="B">B. Another participant is subtracting two
tokens from you<br>
<input type="radio" name="q3" value="C">C. You are subtracting two tokens from another
participant<br>
<input type="radio" name="q3" value="D">D. You are moving too fast<br>
<br><br>

<span class='q4'>Q4. Every time I press the numeric keys between 1-5:</span><br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="A">A. Two tokens are subtracted from my tokens
collected this round<br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="B">B. One token is subtracted from my tokens
collected this round<br>
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="C">C. The background of my yellow dot <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-self.gif"> turns blue
momentarily<br>                                                                                                                             
<input type="radio" name="q4" value="D">D. My yellow dot <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-self.gif"> is paused for two seconds<br>

<input type="submit" name="submit" value="Submit">
</form>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
