<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">5</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">29</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">29</entry>

<entry key='tokens-field-of-vision'>true</entry>
<entry key='subjects-field-of-vision'>true</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
<entry key="regrowth-rate">0.01</entry>

<entry key="chat-enabled">true</entry>
<entry key='voting-and-regulation-enabled'>true</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 2 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
This round is the same as the previous round with two exceptions:
</p>
<ol>
<li>
Before the next round starts you can anonymously communicate by text messages
for four minutes with the other participants in your group. You can use this
opportunity to discuss the experiment and coordinate your actions to improve
your earnings. You may not promise side-payments after the experiment is
completed or make any threats. You are also not allowed to reveal your real
identity. We are monitoring the chat traffic while you chat.
</li>
<li>
During the next round you will have the option to reduce the earnings of another
participant at a cost to your own earnings with constraints depending on the type
of enforcement mechanism used. Below are the 4 types of enforcement mechanisms that 
you have to vote later in the round.
<ol>
<li><b> Everyone can harvest but no sanctioning </b>
<p>In this type all players can harvest but no can sanction or reduce any other
player's tokens</p>
<li><b> Everyone can harvest as well as sanction </b> 
<p>Each time you press the numeric keys between 1-5 the number of tokens of the
corresponding participant is reduced by <b>2</b> with a penalty of <b>1</b> to
yourself.</p>
<p>When you reduce the number of tokens of another participant, they will
receive a message stating that you have reduced their tokens. Likewise, if
another participant reduces your number of tokens, you will also receive a
message. These messages will be displayed on the bottom of your screen.</p>

<li><b> Randomly picked monitoring </b>
<p>Randomly one of the participants is selected to be the monitoring agent
This participant can not harvest, but can force another participant to pay 
<b>1</b> token to the monitoring participant by pressing the responding 
numeric key</p>
<p>At the end of the round each participant who could harvest pays 25% of 
the earning to the monitoring participant.</p>

<li><b> Round Robin monitoring </b>
<p>One participant is assigned the role of the monitor for a period of 48 secs
and others can only harvest. So same rules apply as for the mechanism two. </p>
<p> This continues with each participant getting the chance to be a monitor for 
48 secs </p>
</ol>
</li>
</ol>
<p>
If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="regulation-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Regulation Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
You may now propose a regulation that you wish to have in place during the
round.  After all participants in your group have submitted a regulation you
will be able to vote for a regulation by ranking it from 1 to 5, where 1 is
the most favorable and 5 is the least favorable.
</p>
<ul>
<li>You have 60 seconds to propose a regulation.</li>
<li>Enter your regulation in the text area below.  It will be submitted
automatically once the time ends.</li>
</ul>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="chat-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<p>
You can now chat with the other participants in your group for 4 minutes
total. During the chat round, you may communicate about any aspect of the
experiment that you would like to discuss with other participants with whom
you have been matched. You may not promise them side-payments after the
experiment is completed or threaten them with any consequence after the
experiment is finished. We are monitoring the chat traffic while you chat. If
we see that somebody reveals his or her identity, we have to stop the
experiment and remove the whole group from which this person is a member out
of this room.
</p>
<p>
You will see other participants labeled as "1", "2","3", "4", or "5" in the
chat box.  You can send a chat message by typing into the textfield at the
bottom of the screen and clicking the "send" button with your mouse or
pressing the "enter" key on your keyboard.  
</p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
