<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">26</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">26</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Instructions for Round {roundNumber}</h3>
<hr>
<p>
    The first round of the experiment will begin in a moment. The length of the
    round is {duration}. As in the practice round you can collect green tokens.
    This time you will earn <b>{dollarsPerToken}</b> for each token collected.  This time
    you <b>cannot</b> reset the distribution of green tokens. 
</p>
<h3>Groups</h3>
<hr>
<p>
In this round the renewable resource will become five times bigger.  You will share this
larger environment with three other random players in this room .  In particular,
each of you in this room has been randomly assigned to one of several equal-sized 4
person groups and everyone in your group has been randomly assigned a number from 1
to {clientsPerGroup}.  You will stay in the same group for the entire experiment, and each person's
number from 1 to 4 will remain the same throughout the experiment. The other three people in your group will appear
on the screen as blue dots <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-other.gif"> with a
white number embedded in the dot.
</p>
<p>
    In each round of the token task, you can see how many tokens each player has
    collected at the top right corner of the screen.  On the top left corner of the
    screen you will see the remaining time in the round.
</p>
<h3>Anonymity</h3>
<hr>
<p>
    Because group membership was randomly assigned by the computer, neither you nor
    the experimenter will be able to identify which person in the room has been
    assigned to a particular group or number within a group.  Your anonymity is
    guaranteed.
</p>
<h3>Tokens</h3>
<hr>
    <p>
        Each group has its own set of token resources.
    </p>
<p>
<b>Do you have any questions so far?</b>  If you have any questions at this time,
raise your hand and someone will come over to your station and answer it.
</p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
