<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
    <comment>Communication and Punishment, 3 rounds</comment>
    <entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
    <entry key="clients-per-group">5</entry>
    <entry key="duration">240</entry>
    <entry key="resource-depth">29</entry>
    <entry key="resource-width">29</entry>

    <entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
    <entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

    <entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
    <entry key="regrowth-rate">0.01</entry>
    <entry key="chat-enabled">true</entry>
    <entry key='chat-duration'>240</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-type">real-time</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-cost">1</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-multiplier">2</entry>

    <entry key='repeat'>3</entry>
    <entry key="instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        <h3>Instructions for the Next {self.repeat} Rounds</h3>
        <hr>
        <p>
            The next {self.repeat} rounds are the same as the previous rounds with <b>two exceptions</b>. 
        </p>
        <p>
            You will now be able to communicate with the other participants in your group. Before the next round
            starts you can anonymously communicate via text messages for {self.chatDuration} seconds with the
            other participants in your group. You can use this opportunity to discuss the experiment and
            coordinate your actions to improve your earnings. You may not promise them side-payments after the
            experiment is completed or make any threats. You are also not allowed to reveal your real identity.
            We will be monitoring the chat traffic while you chat.
        </p>
        <p>
            You also have the option to reduce the earnings of another participant at a cost to your own earnings. If
            you press the numeric key 1-5 corresponding to another participant, you will reduce the number of tokens
            they have collected in this round by two tokens. This will also reduce your own token amount by one token.
            The decision whether or when to use this option is up to you. 
        </p>
        <p>
            When you reduce the number of tokens of another participant, they will receive a message stating that you
            have reduced their tokens. Likewise, if another participant reduces your number of tokens, you will also
            receive a message. These messages will be displayed on the bottom of your screen. 
        </p>
        <p>If your tokens are being reduced or you are reducing another participant's tokens, you will receive some
            visual cues.  When your tokens are being reduced your yellow dot will turn red briefly with a blue
            background.  The participant currently reducing your tokens will turn purple with a white background.
        </p>
        <p>You may reduce the earnings of other participants as long as there are tokens remaining on the screen and
            while both you and the other participant have a positive number of tokens collected during the round.
            <b>Each time</b> you press the numeric key corresponding to another participant your token amount is reduced
            by <b>{self.sanctionCost}</b>, and their token amount is reduced by <b>{self.sanctionPenalty}</b>. 
        </p>
        <p>
            The length of this round is again {duration}.
        </p>
        <p>
            If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any questions so far?</b>
        </p>
        ]]>
    </entry>
</properties>
