<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="practice-round">true</entry>
<entry key='resource-width'>8</entry>
<entry key='resource-depth'>8</entry>
<entry key='resource-scale'>32</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>
<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
<entry key="private-property">false</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="quiz-enabled">false</entry>
<entry key="chat-radius">64</entry>
<entry key="seconds-per-year">30</entry>
<entry key="regrowth-rate">.01</entry>
<entry key="tokens-per-fruits">10</entry>
<entry key="experiment-type">forestry</entry>
<entry key="maximum-resource-age">10</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 1 Instructions</h3>
<p>
This is a practice round where you will be able to collect tokens by
harvesting trees and fruit in a 3D representation of a forest.
</p>
<p>
The forest consists of trees which are growing slowly over time. When a tree
is big enough it will generate fruit. You can collect fruit from a tree and
you can cut down a tree. The older the tree the more tokens you collect by
harvesting it. A tree which is one minute old leads to 5 tokens, while a tree
that is four minutes old gives you 25 tokens. After 4 minutes the tree will
not grow any further. If a tree is cut down, it takes some time before a new
seedling generates a new start for a tree to grow. A tree will generate fruits
at age of 5 minutes. You can collect fruits, which generates 10 tokens per
harvest. When you have harvested fruit, new fruit will be added as illustrated
in the figure below. The tree can generate fruit indefinitely.
<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td align="center">
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/trees.jpg"></td>
</tr>
</table> 
You will share the forest with three other participants. You will appear on
the screen as an avatar.
</p>
<p>
<b>Moving your avatar:</b> You can move your avatar by pressing the <b>W</b>,
<b>A</b>, <b>S</b>, <b>D</b> keys or via the arrow keys. <b>W</b> or the
<b>Up</b> arrow key will move your avatar forward while <b>S</b> or the
<b>Down</b> arrow key will move it backward. <b>A</b> or the <b>Left</b> arrow
key will rotate the avatar to its left while <b>D</b> or the <b>Right</b>
arrow key will rotate it to its right.
</p>
<p>
<b>Cutting a tree:</b> Cutting a tree is a two step process.
First you need to select the tree you wish to cut. You can do this by standing
next to the tree and pressing the <b>Q</b> key. You will see the selected tree
changing its color to blue. Then you can cut the selected tree by pressing the
<b>E</b> key. You will see that the avatar moves its axe to cut the tree. The
bigger the tree the more effort the avatar needs to make to cut the tree. When
the tree is cut, you will see tokens added to your total at the top of the
screen. 
</p>
<p>
<b>Collecting fruits:</b> Collecting fruits is also a two step process. 
First you need to select the tree you wish collect fruits from. You can do
this by standing next to the tree and pressing the key <b>Q</b>. You will see
the selected tree changing its color to blue. Then you can collect the fruits
by pressing the key <b>X</b>. You will see that the fruits are falling down,
representing the fruit harvest. On the top of the screen you will see that
tokens are added to your total.
</p>
<p>
<b>Chatting with other players:</b> A chat box is present at the bottom of the
screen. When another player is in the neighborhood, you can click on that
avatar using the left mouse button to start a chat. You will see the character
associated with the selected avatar (<i>A</i>, <i>B</i>, <i>C</i> or <i>D</i>)
appearing in the chat box indicating that you can send messages to that
player.
</p>
<hr>
<h3>Practice Round Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
You will now have four minutes to practice with the experimental environment.
You will share the environment with three other participants. Make sure you
try out the chat option, the cutting of a tree and the collection of fruit.
<p><center><b>Please do not communicate with any other participant.</b></center></p>
<p>If you have any questions please raise your hand. <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b></p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="welcome-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Welcome</h3>
<p>
Welcome. You have already earned 5 dollars for showing up at this experiment.
You can earn more, up to a maximum of 40 dollars, by participating in this
experiment, which will take about an hour.  The amount of money you earn
depends on your decisions as well as the decisions of your group members
during the four rounds of the experiment.
</p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
