<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Costly Sanctioning XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="hostname">@SERVER_ADDRESS@</entry>
<entry key="port">@PORT_NUMBER@</entry>
<entry key="round0">round0.xml</entry>
<entry key="round1">round1.xml</entry>
<entry key="round2">round2.xml</entry>
<entry key="round3">round3.xml</entry>
<entry key="round4">round4.xml</entry>
<entry key="round5">round5.xml</entry>
<entry key="round6">round6.xml</entry>
<entry key="wait-for-participants">true</entry>
<entry key="number-of-rounds">7</entry>
<entry key="facilitator-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Facilitator Instructions</h3>
<p>
Welcome to the facilitator interface.  This interface allows you to control
the experiment.  You may only modify configuration parameters <b>before</b>
you start the experiment by selecting the Configuration menu.  When all the
participants are ready to begin the experiment, you can start the experiment
by selecting Experiment -&gt; Start.  After a round has been completed you
will be able to view the statistics for all of the participants.  You can
begin the next round by selecting Round -&gt; Start.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='field-of-vision-instructions'>
<![CDATA[
Your vision is limited in this experiment.  The area that is visible to you will be
shaded.
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="welcome-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Welcome</h1>
<hr>
<p>
Welcome to the experiment. The experiment will begin shortly after everyone has been
assigned a station.
<br><br>
Please <b>wait quietly</b> and <b>do not close this window or open any other applications</b>.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="general-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h1>General Instructions</h1>
<p>
Welcome. You have already earned 5 dollars by showing up at this experiment. You can
earn more, up to a maximum of about 40 dollars, by participating in this experiment, which
will take about an hour to an hour and a half. The amount of money you earn depends
on your decisions as well as the decisions of other people in this room during the
six rounds of the experiment. 
</p>
<p>
You will appear on the screen as a yellow dot <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-self.gif"></img>. 
You can move by pressing the four arrow keys on your keyboard.  You can move up,
down, left, or right.  You have to press a key for each and every move of your
yellow dot.  In this experiment you can collect green diamond shaped tokens 
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-token.gif"></img> and earn two cents for each collected token.  
To collect a token, move your yellow dot over a green token and <b>press the space
bar</b>.  Simply moving your avatar over a token does NOT collect that token.
</p>

<p>
The tokens that you collect have the potential to regenerate.  After you have
collected a green token, a new token can re-appear on that empty cell. The rate at
which new tokens appear is dependent on the number of adjacent cells with tokens.
The more tokens in the eight cells that surround an empty cell, the faster a new
token will appear on that empty cell.  In other words, <b>existing tokens can
generate new tokens</b>.  To illustrate this, please refer to Image 1 and Image 2.
The middle cell in Image 1 denoted with an X has a greater chance of regeneration
than the middle cell in Image 2.  When all neighboring cells are empty, there is
<b>no chance for regeneration</b>.
</p>

<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td align="center"><b>Image 1</b></td>
<td align="center"><b>Image 2</b></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center">
    <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/8neighbors.jpg" alt="image 1"></img>
</td>
<td align="center">
    <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/5neighbors.jpg" alt="image 2"></img>
</td>
</tr>
</table>

<h2>Best Strategy</h2>
<hr>
<p>
The chance that a token will regenerate on an empty cell increases as there are
more tokens surrounding it.  Therefore, you want to have as many tokens around an
empty cell as possible.  However, you also need empty cells to benefit from this
regrowth.  The optimal spatial pattern of tokens on the screen is the checkerboard
diagram shown below, where half of the cells are empty and arranged in a way that
maximizes regrowth.
<br>
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/optimal-strategy.jpg" alt="Checkerboard Resource"></img>
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='trust-game-instructions'>
<![CDATA[
<h1>Trust Game Instructions</h1>
<hr>
<p>
    You will now play a mini-game where you will be matched with a random person in
    your group. In this game there are two roles, Player 1 and Player 2.  Your job
    is to design strategies for both Player 1 and Player 2 roles.  When you are
    randomly paired with another member of your group you may be selected as Player
    1 <b>or</b> Player 2.  The results of your strategies will be shown to you at
    the <b>end of the experiment</b>.
</p>

<h2>Game Mechanics</h2>
<hr>
<p>
The game works as follows:
</p>
<ol>
    <li>Player 1 first receives an endowment of one dollar and has to decide <b>how much to keep</b> and <b>how much to send to Player 2</b>.
    <li>The amount Player 1 decides to send to Player 2 is tripled by
        the system and then given to Player 2.  Player 2 then has to decide <b>how
            much to keep</b> and <b>how much to send back to Player 1</b>.
</ol>
<p>
For example, if Player 1 sends 0 cents to Player 2, Player 1 earns 1 dollar and
Player 2 earns 0 cents. However, if Player 1 sends 1 dollar to Player 2, 3 dollars
would be sent to Player 2.  Player 2 then decides to return $1.75 back to Player 1.
In this case, Player 1 earns $1.75, and Player 2 earns $1.25.
</p>
<p>
Please fill in the following form to design your strategies as Player 1 or Player 2.
<br>
<b>If you have any questions, please raise your hand.  Are there any questions?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
