<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">26</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">26</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
<entry key='voting-enabled'>true</entry>
<entry key='initial-voting-instructions'>
    <![CDATA[
<h1>Notice</h1>
<hr>
<p>
In a moment, you will see a screen on your computer called Rule Options. It
will list 6 different rules that you can consider as options for managing how
each of your groups collect green tokens today. 
</p>
<p>
You can nominate one rule from the list to help decide whether or not to have a
rule and what that rule will be. The rule that has the most nominations will be
considered chosen and established as the rule. If there is a tie, then each
tied nominated rule will receive an equal chance of getting selected at random.
</p>
    ]]>
</entry>

<entry key='voting-instructions'>
<![CDATA[
<h1>Voting Instructions</h1>
<hr>
<p>
To nominate a rule, click the radio button to the left of the one you choose, and
then click "submit." The computer will tally the nominations and then report
the results on the next screen. The results will be presented to each
participant in your group and the experimenter.
</p>

<p>
The identity of people who nominated a particular rule will NOT be revealed.
Therefore, neither you nor the experimenter will know who nominated a
particular rule.
</p>

</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='external-survey-enabled'>true</entry>
<entry key='survey-instructions'>
    <![CDATA[
    <h1>Survey</h1>
    <hr>
        <p>
            Before we continue to the next round of the token task, we would like to ask you
            some quick questions.  At the beginning of the survey you will need to enter:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Your player ID: {participantId} </li>
            <li>Your survey ID: {surveyId} </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Please <a href='{surveyLink}'>click here</a> to begin the survey.
        </p>
    ]]>
</entry>

<entry key='survey-link'>
    <![CDATA[
    https://qtrial.qualtrics.com/SE/?SID=SV_38lReBOv0Wk7wgY
    ]]>
</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 4 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
    Round 4 is about to begin.  
</p>

<p>
The length of this round is four minutes.
</p>
<p>
If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>

</properties>
