<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">4</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">26</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">26</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>

<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 5 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
Round 5 is the same as round 4.</p>
<p>
The length of this round is again four minutes.
</p>
<p>
If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='sanction-type'>REAL_TIME</entry>
<entry key="sanction-cost">1</entry>
<entry key="sanction-multiplier">2</entry>
<entry key='sanction-instructions'>
    <![CDATA[
    <h1>Instructions</h1>
    <hr>
<p>
During this upcoming round you will have the option to reduce the earnings of
another participant at a cost to your own earnings.
</p>
<h2>How it works</h2>
<hr>
    <ul>
        <li>If you press the numeric key 1-5 corresponding to another participant, you
            will reduce the number of tokens they have collected in this round by two
            tokens. This will also reduce your own token amount by one token. The decision
            whether or when to use this option is up to you. 
        </li>
        <li>When you reduce the number of tokens of another participant, they will
            receive a message stating that you have reduced their tokens. Likewise, if
            another participant reduces your number of tokens, you will also receive a
            message. These messages will be displayed on the bottom of your screen.
        </li>
        <li>If your tokens are being reduced or you are reducing another participant's
            tokens, you will receive some visual cues.  When your tokens are being reduced
            your yellow dot will turn red briefly with a blue background.  The participant
            currently reducing your tokens will turn purple with a white background.
        </li>
        <li>You may reduce the earnings of other participants as long as there are
            tokens remaining on the screen and while both you and the other participant
            have a positive number of tokens collected during the round.  <b>Each time</b>
            you press the numeric key corresponding to another participant your token
            amount is reduced by <b>one</b>, and their token amount is reduced by
            <b>two</b>.  
        </li>
    </ul>
    ]]>
</entry>
</properties>
