<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
    <comment>First group round, chat enabled</comment>
    <entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
    <entry key="clients-per-group">2</entry>
    <entry key="duration">240</entry>
    <entry key="resource-depth">13</entry>
    <entry key="resource-width">13</entry>
    <entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
    <entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>
    <entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
    <entry key="regrowth-rate">0.01</entry>
    <!-- before this round begins, we have a chat session -->
    <entry key="chat-enabled">true</entry>
    <entry key="chat-duration">120</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-type">real-time</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-cost">1</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-multiplier">2</entry>
    <entry key='repeat'>6</entry>
    <entry key="quiz">true</entry>
    <entry key="q1">C</entry>

    <entry key="instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Instructions</h1>

        <p>



            {if (baselineTreatment)}
             Baseline treatment!
            {endif}

            {if (rangeTreatment)}
             Range treatment!
            {endif}


            {if (divergenceTreatment)}
             Divergence treatment!
            {endif}



            The length of each of the following {self.repeat} rounds is {self.duration} seconds. As in the practice
            round you can collect green tokens but there are two important differences. You will earn
            <b>{dollarsPerToken}</b> for each token collectede and you <b>cannot reset</b> the distribution of
            green tokens. Group:
        </p>
        <p>
            In this round the renewable resource will become five times bigger. You
            will share this larger environment with other players in this room.
            Each of you has been randomly assigned to one of several equal-sized
            {self.clientsPerGroup}-person groups.  Each of the groups is collecting tokens from an identical, but
            separate resource. 
        </p>
        <p>
            Each of you has been assigned a number from 1 to {self.clientsPerGroup}.  The other members of your
            group will appear on the screen as blue circles <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/blue-circle.png"> with a
            white number in the middle of the circle.  On the top right corner of the screen you can see how many tokens
            each player has collected.
        </p>
        <h3>Anonymity</h3>
        <hr>
        <p>
            Because group membership was randomly assigned by the computer, neither you nor
            the experimenter will be able to identify which person in the room has been
            assigned to a particular group or number within a group.  Your anonymity is
            guaranteed.
        </p>
        <p>
            Before the next round starts you can anonymously communicate via text messages
            for four minutes with the other participants in your group. You can use this
            opportunity to discuss the experiment and coordinate your actions to improve
            your earnings. You may not promise them side-payments after the experiment is
            completed or make any threats. You are also not allowed to reveal your real
            identity. We will be monitoring the chat traffic while you chat.
        </p>

      
        <p>
            If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any questions so far?</b>
        </p>
        ]]>
    </entry>
    <entry key="quiz-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h2>Experimental instructions</h2>
<hr>
<p>
  Empty cells have each second the potential to generate new tokens. The probability that a given empty cell will generate a token is density-dependent on the number of adjacent cells with tokens. The probability Pt is linearly related to the number of neighbors: Pt = p*N=nt/N where nt is the number of neighboring cells containing a green token, and N is the number of neighboring cells (N=8).Based on years of rigorous studies, a group of scientists finds that the estimated range of the token regeneration rate is 0.01.

</p>
<br>
<form>
<span class='q1'>Q1. Which of the following statement is correct?</span> <br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="A">A. Token regeneration rate will vary over time in each round.<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="B">B. Scientists suggest different possibilities of token regeneration within the bounds.<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="C">C. Scientists know the point estimate of the token regeneration rate.<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="D">D. Token regeneration rate is very high. <br>
<br>
<input type="submit" name="submit" value="Submit"><br>
</form>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='quiz-results'>
    <![CDATA[
    <h2>Quiz Results</h2>
    <hr>
        <p>
            {if (allCorrect)}
            You have answered all the questions correctly and earned <b>{totalQuizEarnings}</b>.  
            {else}
            You answered {numberCorrect} out of {totalQuestions} questions correctly and earned <b>{totalQuizEarnings}</b>.  Questions you've answered
            incorrectly are highlighted in red.  Please see below for more details.
            {endif}
        </p>
        <br><hr>
<form>
<span class='q1'>Q1. Which of these statements is NOT correct?</span> <br>
    <b>{incorrect_q1}

        Insert here an explanation.
        
    </b>
<br>
A. Token regeneration rate will vary over time in each round.<br>
B. Scientists suggest different possibilities of token regeneration within the bounds.<br>
C. Scientists know the point estimate of the token regeneration rate.<br>
D. Token regeneration rate is very high.
<br>

<input type="submit" name="submit" value="Next page"><br>

</form>
    ]]>
</entry>

</properties>
