<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
    <comment>First group round, chat enabled</comment>
    <entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
    <entry key="clients-per-group">5</entry>
    <entry key="duration">240</entry>
    <entry key="resource-depth">29</entry>
    <entry key="resource-width">29</entry>
    <entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
    <entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>
    <entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>
    <entry key="regrowth-rate">0.01</entry>
    <!-- before this round begins, we have a chat session -->
    <entry key="chat-enabled">true</entry>
    <entry key="chat-duration">240</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-type">real-time</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-cost">1</entry>
    <entry key="sanction-multiplier">2</entry>
    <entry key='repeat'>3</entry>
    <entry key="instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Instructions for Rounds 1-{self.repeat}</h1>
        <hr>
        <p>
            The length of each of the following {self.repeat} rounds is {self.duration} seconds. As in the practice
            round you can collect green tokens but there are two important differences. You will earn
            <b>{dollarsPerToken}</b> for each token collected and you <b>cannot reset</b> the distribution of
            green tokens. 
        </p>
        <p>
            In this round the renewable resource will become five times bigger. You
            will share this larger environment with other players in this room.
            Each of you has been randomly assigned to one of several equal-sized
            {self.clientsPerGroup}-person groups.  Each of the groups is collecting tokens from an identical, but
            separate resource. 
        </p>
        <p>
            Each of you has been assigned a number from 1 to {self.clientsPerGroup}.  The other members of your
            group will appear on the screen as blue circles <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/blue-circle.png"> with a
            white number in the middle of the circle.  On the top right corner of the screen you can see how many tokens
            each player has collected.
        </p>
        <h3>Anonymity</h3>
        <hr>
        <p>
            Because group membership was randomly assigned by the computer, neither you nor
            the experimenter will be able to identify which person in the room has been
            assigned to a particular group or number within a group.  Your anonymity is
            guaranteed.
        </p>
        <p>
            Before the next round starts you can anonymously communicate via text messages
            for four minutes with the other participants in your group. You can use this
            opportunity to discuss the experiment and coordinate your actions to improve
            your earnings. You may not promise them side-payments after the experiment is
            completed or make any threats. You are also not allowed to reveal your real
            identity. We will be monitoring the chat traffic while you chat.
        </p>
        <p>
            You also have the option to reduce the earnings of another participant at a cost to your own earnings. If
            you press the numeric key 1-5 corresponding to another participant, you will reduce the number of tokens
            they have collected in this round by two tokens. This will also reduce your own token amount by one token.
            The decision whether or when to use this option is up to you. 
        </p>
        <p>
            When you reduce the number of tokens of another participant, they will receive a message stating that you
            have reduced their tokens. Likewise, if another participant reduces your number of tokens, you will also
            receive a message. These messages will be displayed on the bottom of your screen. 
        </p>
        <p>If your tokens are being reduced or you are reducing another participant's tokens, you will receive some
            visual cues.  When your tokens are being reduced your yellow dot will turn red briefly with a blue
            background.  The participant currently reducing your tokens will turn purple with a white background.
        </p>
        <p>You may reduce the earnings of other participants as long as there are tokens remaining on the screen and
            while both you and the other participant have a positive number of tokens collected during the round.
            <b>Each time</b> you press the numeric key corresponding to another participant your token amount is reduced
            by <b>{self.sanctionCost}</b>, and their token amount is reduced by <b>{self.sanctionPenalty}</b>. 
        </p>
        <p>
            If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any questions so far?</b>
        </p>
        ]]>
    </entry>
</properties>
