<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="resource-width">13</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">13</entry>
<entry key="practice-round">true</entry>
<entry key="private-property">true</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>

<entry key='regrowth-rate'>.01</entry>
<entry key='initial-distribution'>.25</entry>
<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>

<entry key="quiz">true</entry>
<entry key="q1">C</entry>
<entry key="q2">B</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>General Instructions</h3>
<p>
You appear on the screen as a yellow dot <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-self.gif">, 
and your other group members appear as blue dots <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-other.gif">.
You move by pressing the four arrow keys to the right of your keyboard.  You
can move either up, down, left, or right.  You have to press a key for every
move of your yellow dot.  In this experiment you can collect green diamond
shaped tokens 
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-token.gif"> and you will
earn two cents for each collected token.  To collect a token, simply move your
yellow dot over a green token and press the <b>space bar</b>.  If you move
over a token without pressing the <b>space bar</> you will NOT collect that
token.
</p>

<p>
The tokens that you collect have the potential to regenerate.  After you have
collected a green token, a new token can once again appear on that empty cell.
However, the rate at which new tokens will appear depends on the number of
adjacent cells that still have tokens.  The more tokens in the 8 cells around
an empty cel, the faster a new token will appear on that empty cell.  Tokens
generate new tokens.  Thus the middle cell in Image 1 denoted with X will be
regenerated at a faster rate than the middle cell in Image 2.  When all
neighboring cells are empty, there is no renewal.

<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td align="center"><b>Image 1</b></td>
<td align="center"><b>Image 2</b></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center">
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/8neighbors.jpg" alt="image 1">
</td>
<td align="center">
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/5neighbors.jpg" alt="image 2">
</td>
</tr>
</table>
<hr>
<h3>Practice Round Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
You will now have four minutes to practice with the experimental environment.
The decisions you make in this round will NOT influence your earnings.  At the
At the beginning of the practice round half of the cells are occupied
with green tokens.  The environment is a 13 x 13 grid of cells.
</p>
<p>
When you push the <b>R</b> key you will reset the distribution of
the tokens to randomly occupying half of the cells with green tokens.
</p>

<p><center><b>Please do not communicate with any other participant.</b></center></p>
<p>If you have any questions please raise your hand. <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b></p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="quiz-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<p>
Before we begin the practice round you need to answer the following questions
correctly. You can only continue when you have answered all questions
correctly.  If an error is made you will need to answer the questions again.
</p>
<br>
<form>
Which of the statements is incorrect? <br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="A">Your decisions of where to collect tokens affect the regeneration of tokens.<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="B">When you have collected all tokens on
the screen, no new tokens will appear.<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="C">Tokens grow from the middle of the
screen.<br>
<input type="radio" name="q1" value="D">In order to collect a token you need
to press the space bar while your avatar is on a cell with a token.<br>
<br><br>

Which sequence of situations is not possible? <br>
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/question2.jpg"><br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="A">A<br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="B">B<br>
<input type="radio" name="q2" value="C">C<br>
<br>
<input type="submit" name="submit" value="Submit">
</form>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="welcome-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Welcome</h3>
<p>
Welcome. You have already earned 5 dollars for showing up at this experiment.
You can earn more, up to a maximum of 40 dollars, by participating in this
experiment, which will take about an hour.  The amount of money you earn
depends on your decisions as well as the decisions of your group members
during the four rounds of the experiment.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

</properties>
