<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Foraging XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="display-group-tokens">true</entry>
<entry key="clients-per-group">5</entry>
<entry key="resource-depth">29</entry>
<entry key="resource-width">29</entry>
<entry key="duration">240</entry>

<!-- have a trust game before this round begins -->
<entry key='trust-game'>true</entry>
<!-- enable field of vision for tokens and subjects -->

<entry key='always-explicit'>true</entry>
<entry key='max-cell-occupancy'>1</entry>

<entry key='in-round-chat-enabled'>true</entry>
<entry key="initial-distribution">.25</entry>

<entry key="instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Round 4 Instructions</h3>
<hr>
<p>
    Round 4 is the same as the previous rounds with one exception.  You will be able
    to communicate with the other participants in your group <b>during</b> the
    round.  To communicate, hit the enter key, type uour message, and then hit the
    enter key again.  You must hit the enter key before every message you type,
    otherwise control will return to the game screen where you can use the arrow
    keys to move around.
</p>

<p>
The length of this round is four minutes.
</p>
<p>
If you have any questions please raise your hand.  <b>Do you have any
questions so far?</b>
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="chat-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<p>
You can chat with the other participants in your group during this round.
You may communicate about any aspect of the experiment that you would like to
discuss with other participants with whom you have been matched. You may not promise
them side-payments after the experiment is completed or threaten them with any
consequence after the experiment is finished. We are monitoring the chat traffic
while you chat. If we see that somebody reveals his or her identity, we have to stop
the experiment and remove the whole group from which this person is a member out of
this room.
</p>
<p>
You will see other participants labeled as "1", "2","3", "4", or "5" in the chat
box.  You can send a chat message by typing into the textfield and pressing the
enter key.
</p>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
