<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>Costly Sanctioning XML-ized experiment round configuration</comment>
<entry key="hostname">@SERVER_ADDRESS@</entry>
<entry key="port">@PORT_NUMBER@</entry>
<entry key="round0">round0.xml</entry>
<entry key="round1">round1.xml</entry>
<entry key="round2">round2.xml</entry>
<entry key="round3">round3.xml</entry>
<entry key="round4">round4.xml</entry>
<entry key="round5">round5.xml</entry>
<entry key="round6">round6.xml</entry>
<entry key="wait-for-participants">true</entry>
<entry key="number-of-rounds">7</entry>
<entry key="facilitator-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Facilitator Instructions</h3>
<p>
Welcome to the facilitator interface.  This interface allows you to control
the experiment.  You may only modify configuration parameters <b>before</b>
you start the experiment by selecting the Configuration menu.  When all the
participants are ready to begin the experiment, you can start the experiment
by selecting Experiment -&gt; Start.  After a round has been completed you
will be able to view the statistics for all of the participants.  You can
begin the next round by selecting Round -&gt; Start.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='censored-chat-instructions'>
<![CDATA[
<p>
Your messages must first be approved before they will be relayed to the rest of your group.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="chat-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<p>
You can now chat with the other participants in your group for 4 minutes
total. During the chat round, you may communicate about any aspect of the
experiment that you would like to discuss with other participants with whom
you have been matched. You may not promise them side-payments after the
experiment is completed or threaten them with any consequence after the
experiment is finished. We are monitoring the chat traffic while you chat. If we
detect any violation of these rules, we will stop the experiment and remove the
offending group from the room.
</p>
<p>
You will see other participants labeled as "1", "2","3", "4", or "5" in the
chat box.  You can send a chat message by typing into the textfield at the
bottom of the screen and pressing the "enter" key on your keyboard.  
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key='field-of-vision-instructions'>
<![CDATA[
Your vision is limited in this experiment.  The area that is visible to you will be
shaded.
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="welcome-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Welcome to the experiment. The experiment will begin shortly after everyone has been
assigned a station.</h3>
<p>
Please <b>wait quietly</b> and <b>do not close this window or open any other applications</b>.
</p>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="general-instructions">
<![CDATA[
<h3>General Instructions</h3>
<p>
Welcome. You have already earned 5 dollars by showing up at this experiment. You can
earn more, up to a maximum of 40 dollars, by participating in this experiment, which
will take about an hour to an hour and a half. The amount of money you earn depends
on your decisions as well as the decisions of other people in this room during the
six rounds of the experiment. 
</p>
<p>
You appear on the screen as a yellow dot <img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-self.gif">. 
You move by pressing the four arrow keys on your keyboard.  You can move up, down,
left, or right.  You have to press a key for each and every move of your yellow dot.  
In this experiment you can collect green diamond shaped tokens 
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/gem-token.gif"> and earn two cents for each collected token.  
To collect a token, move your yellow dot over a green token and press the <b>space
bar</b>.  If you move over a token without pressing the <b>space bar</> you do NOT
collect that token.
</p>

<p>
The tokens that you collect have the potential to regenerate.  After you have
collected a green token, a new token can re-appear on that empty cell.
However, the rate at which new tokens will appear depends on the number of
adjacent cells with tokens.  The more tokens in the eight cells around
an empty cell, the faster a new token will appear on that empty cell.  In other
words, <b>existing tokens can generate new tokens</b>.  To illustrate this, please
refer to Image 1 and Image 2.  The middle cell in Image 1 denoted with an X has
a greater chance of regeneration than the middle cell in Image 2.  When all
neighboring cells are empty, there is <b>no chance for regeneration</b>.

<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td align="center"><b>Image 1</b></td>
<td align="center"><b>Image 2</b></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center">
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/8neighbors.jpg" alt="image 1">
</td>
<td align="center">
<img src="@CODEBASE_URL@/images/5neighbors.jpg" alt="image 2">
</td>
</tr>
</table>
]]>
</entry>


</properties>
